Finding Aid for the Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo, 2016
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Composer David Felder coaches the Arditti Quartet (Irvine Arditti, violin, Ashot Sarkissjan, violin, Lucas Fels, violoncello, Ralf Ehlers, viola) on Felder's Netivot as Olivier Pasquet, electronics listens at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4362.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_172.tif)
- Composer David Felder coaches the Arditti Quartet (Irvine Arditti, violin, Ashot Sarkissjan, violin, Lucas Fels, violoncello, Ralf Ehlers, viola) on Felder's Netivot as Olivier Pasquet, electronics listens at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4363.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_173.tif)
- Composer David Felder and Olivier Pasquet, electronics watch as the Arditti Quartet (Ralf Ehlers, viola, Lucas Fels, violoncello, Ashot Sarkissjan, violin, and Irvine Arditti, violin) rehearse Felder's Netivot at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4364.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_174.tif)
- Composer David Felder and Olivier Pasquet, electronics, watch the Arditti Quartet rehearse Felder's Netivot at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4366.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_175.tif)
- Composer David Felder coaches the Arditti Quartet (Irvine Arditti, violin, Ashot Sarkissjan, violin, Lucas Fels, violoncello, Ralf Ehlers, viola) on Felder's Netivot at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4367.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_176.tif)
- Composer David Felder coaches Katie Schoepflin, clarinet of Ensemble Dal Niente on Felder's Rare air at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4370 David Felder RAIR AIR.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_177.tif)
- Composer David Felder coaches Katie Schoepflin, clarinet of Ensemble Dal Niente on Felder's Rare air at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4373David Felder RARE AIR.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_178.tif)
- Katie Schoepflin, clarinet of Ensemble Dal Niente rehearses David Felder's Rare air at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4374.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_179.tif)
- Katie Schoepflin, clarinet of Ensemble Dal Niente rehearses David Felder's Rare air at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4375.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_180.tif)
- Composer David Felder coaches Katie Schoepflin, clarinet of Ensemble Dal Niente on Felder's Rare air at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4377.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_181.tif)
- J.T. Rinker and Chris Jacobs assist with electronics while Katie Schoepflin, clarinet of Ensemble Dal Niente rehearses David Felder's Rare air at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4379Chris Jacobs, JT Rinker rehearsal.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_182.tif)
- Katie Schoepflin, clarinet of Ensemble Dal Niente rehearses David Felder's Rare air at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4380.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_183.tif)
- Composer David Felder coaches Katie Schoepflin, clarinet of Ensemble Dal Niente on Felder's Rare air at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4381.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_184.tif)
- Composer David Felder coaches Katie Schoepflin, clarinet of Ensemble Dal Niente on Felder's Rare air at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4385.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_185.tif)
- Mabel Kwan, piano and Katie Schoepflin, clarinet of Ensemble Dal Niente rehearse David Felder's Rare air at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4389.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_186.tif)
- Katie Schoepflin, clarinet and Mabel Kwan, piano of Ensemble Dal Niente rehearse David Felder's Rare air at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4392.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_187.tif)
- Composer David Felder coaches Katie Schoepflin, clarinet and Mabel Kwan, piano of Ensemble Dal Niente rehearse Felder's Rare air at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4394.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_188.tif)
- Katie Schoepflin, clarinet of Ensemble Dal Niente packs up after rehearsal of David Felder's Rare Ari at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4398.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_189.tif)
- Conductor Jozsef Hars and members of Ensemble Uusinta (Max Savikangas, viola, Pinja Laine, violoncello, and Väinö Jalkanen, piano, rehearse student composer Young Woo Yoo's String Trio at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4401.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_190.tif)
- Stephen Solook, percussion, looks over a percussion setup at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4402.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_191.tif)
- Percussion setup at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4403.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_192.tif)
- John Smigielski, percussion works in a percussion setup at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4404.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_193.tif)
- Sheet music for Josh Levine's Former Selves at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4406.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_194.tif)
- Composer Hans Abrahamsen coaches Michael Lewanski, conductor and Tam Travers, violin of Ensemble Dal Niente on Abrahamsen's Winternacht at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4409.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_195.tif)
- Composer Hans Abrahamsen coaches Michael Lewanski, conductor and Tam Travers, violin of Ensemble Dal Niente on Abrahamsen's Winternacht at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4415.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_196.tif)
- Composer Hans Abrahamsen coaches Michael Lewanski, conductor and Tam Travers, violin of Ensemble Dal Niente on Abrahamsen's Winternacht at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4417.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_197.tif)
- Composer Hans Abrahamsen coaches Michael Lewanski, conductor and Tam Travers, violin of Ensemble Dal Niente on Abrahamsen's Winternacht at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4420.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_198.tif)
- Composer Hans Abrahamsen coaches Michael Lewanski, conductor and Ensemble Dal Niente (Tam Travers, violin, Emma Hospelhorn, flute, Magnus Andersson, guitar, Katie Schoepflin, clarinet, Chris Wild, violoncello, Greg Byer, percussion) on Abrahamsen's Winternacht at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4421.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_199.tif)
- Composer Hans Abrahamsen coaches Michael Lewanski, conductor and Ensemble Dal Niente (Tam Travers, violin, Emma Hospelhorn, flute, Magnus Andersson, guitar, Katie Schoepflin, clarinet, Chris Wild, violoncello, Greg Byer, percussion) on Abrahamsen's Winternacht at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4422.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_200.tif)
- Conductor Michael Lewanski leads Ensemble Dal Niente (Greg Beyer, percussion, Katie Schoepflin, clarinet, Mabel Kwan, piano, Chris Wild, violoncello, Emma Hospelhorn, flute, and Tam Travers, violin) in rehearsal of Hans Abrahamsen's Winternacht at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4426.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_201.tif)
- Composer Hans Abrahamsen watches as Michael Lewanski, conductor leads Ensemble Dal Niente (Mabel Kwan, piano, Tam Travers, violin, Emma Hospelhorn, flute, Magnus Andersson, guitar, Katie Schoepflin, clarinet, Chris Wild, violoncello, and Greg Beyer, percussion) in rehearsal of Abrahamsen's Winternacht at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4427.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_202.tif)
- Composer Joshua Fineberg coaches Michael Lewanski, conductor and Ensemble Dal Niente (Emma Hospelhorn, flute, Katie Schoepflin, clarinet) on Fineberg's piece Paradigms at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4432Joshua Fineberg.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_203.tif)
- Cover of Mabel Kwan's piano music for composer Chinary Ung's Singing inside aura with Ensemble Dal Niente members Emma Hospelhorn, flute, Katie Schoepflin, clarinet, and Tam Travers, violin, in the background at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4433.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_204.tif)
- Susan Ung, viola rehearses Chinary Ung's Singing inside aura at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4435 Susan UNG.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_205.tif)
- Susan Ung, viola rehearses Chinary Ung's Singing inside aura at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4436.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_206.tif)
- Susan Ung, viola rehearses Chinary Ung's Singing inside aura at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4439.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_207.tif)
- Susan Ung, viola rehearses Chinary Ung's Singing inside aura with Greg Beyer, percussion of Ensemble Dal Niente at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4445.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_208.tif)
- Susan Ung, viola rehearses Chinary Ung's Singing inside aura at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4448 copy.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_209.tif)
- Susan Ung, viola rehearses Chinary Ung's Singing inside aura at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4450.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_210.tif)
- Susan Ung, viola rehearses Chinary Ung's Singing inside aura at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4454.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_211.tif)
- Susan Ung, viola rehearses Chinary Ung's Singing inside aura at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4461.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_212.tif)
- Susan Ung, viola rehearses Chinary Ung's Singing inside aura at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4462.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_213.tif)
- Susan Ung, viola rehearses Chinary Ung's Singing inside aura at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name rehearsal with Susan Ung copy.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_214.tif)
- Stephen Solook and Greg Beyer, percussion of Ensemble Dal Niente rehearse Chinary Ung's Singing inside aura at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4465.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_215.tif)
- Stephen Solook and Greg Beyer, percussion of Ensemble Dal Niente rehearse Chinary Ung's Singing inside aura with Susan Ung, viola at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4468.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_216.tif)
- Conductor Michael Lewanski leads Susan Ung, viola and Stephen Solook, percussion in Ensemble Dal Niente's rehearsal of Chinary Ung's Singing inside aura at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4476.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_217.tif)
- Conductor Michael Lewanski leads Ensemble Dal Niente (Greg Beyer, percussion, Emma Hospelhorn, flute, Katie Schoepflin, clarinet) in rehearsal of Chinary Ung's Singing inside aura at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4477.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_218.tif)
- Conductor Michael Lewanski leads Susan Ung, viola and Ensemble Dal Niente (Greg Beyer, percussion, Katie Schoepflin, clarinet, and Stephen Solook, percussion) in rehearsal of Chinary Ung's Singing inside aura at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4478.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_219.tif)
- Conductor Michael Lewanski leads Susan Ung, viola and Ensemble Dal Niente (Greg Beyer, percussion, Katie Schoepflin, clarinet, and Stephen Solook, percussion) in rehearsal of Chinary Ung's Singing inside aura at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4479.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_220.tif)
- Conductor Michael Lewanski leads Susan Ung, viola and Ensemble Dal Niente (Greg Beyer, percussion, Katie Schoepflin, clarinet, and Stephen Solook, percussion) in rehearsal of Chinary Ung's Singing inside aura at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4482.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_221.tif)
- Conductor Michael Lewanski leads Susan Ung, viola and Ensemble Dal Niente (Emma Hospelhorn, flute, Greg Beyer, percussion, Katie Schoepflin, clarinet, Chris wild, violoncello, and Mabel Kwan, piano) in rehearsal of Chinary Ung's Singing inside aura at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4485.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_222.tif)
- Susan Ung, viola and Ensemble Dal Niente (Greg Beyer, percussion, Katie Schoepflin, clarinet, Chris Wild, violoncello, Mabel Kwan, piano, Stephen Solook, percussion) in rehearsal of Chinary Ung's Singing inside aura at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4486.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_223.tif)
- Susan Ung, viola and Ensemble Dal Niente (Greg Beyer, percussion, Katie Schoepflin, clarinet, Chris Wild, violoncello, and Stephen Solook, percussion) rehearse Chinary Ung's Singing inside aura at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4487.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_224.tif)
- Composer Chinary Ung coaches Michael Lewanski, conductor and Ensemble Dal Niente (Emma Hospelhorn, flute, Chris Wild, violoncello, and Tam Travers, violin) in rehearsal of Ung's Singing inside aura at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4492.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_225.tif)
- Composer Chinary Ung coaches Susan Ung, viola and Ensemble Dal Niente (Tam Travers, violin, Chris Wild, violoncello, Stephen Solook, percussion, Katie Schoepflin, clarinet, Emma Hospelhorn, flute, and Greg Beyer, percussion) on Ung's Singing inside aura as Michael Lewanski, conductor at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4496.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_226.tif)
- Composer Chinary Ung coaches Susan Ung, viola and Ensemble Dal Niente (Tam Travers, violin, Chris Wild, violoncello, Stephen Solook, percussion) on Ung's Singing inside aura as Michael Lewanski, conductor at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4497.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_227.tif)
- Composer Chinary Ung coaches Ensemble Dal Niente (Katie Schoepflin, clarinet, Chris Wild, violoncello, Emma Hospelhorn, flute, and Tam Travers, violin) on Ung's piece Singing inside aura at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4498.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_228.tif)
- Composer Chinary Ung coaches Ensemble Dal Niente on Ung's Singing inside aura at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4499.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_229.tif)
- Composer Chinary Ung coaches Ensemble Dal Niente on Ung's Singing inside aura at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4500.jpg Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_230.tif)
- Composer Chinary Ung coaches Ensemble Dal Niente on Ung's Singing inside aura at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4500.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_231.tif)
- Composer Chinary Ung coaches Ensemble Dal Niente on Ung's Singing inside aura at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4501 copy.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_232.tif)
- Composer Chinary Ung coaches Ensemble Dal Niente on Ung's Singing inside aura at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4501.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_233.tif)
- Composer Chinary Ung coaches percussionist Greg Beyer of Ensemble Dal Niente on Ung's Singing inside aura at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4504 copy.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_234.tif)
- Conductor Michael Lewanski leads Ensemble Dal Niente (Tam Travers, violin, Mabel Kwan, piano, Chris Wild, violoncello, Katie Schoepflin, clarinet, and Emma Hospelhorn, flute) in performance at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4512.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_235.tif)